Jai Hind friends, welcome to
your own YouTube channel Gyan Josh
and in this video I am going to tell you
about Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Company Limited Recruitment 2021 which has been
recently released and in which
candidates will be able to apply from all India
and let me tell you that to apply in this,
you are only asked for 12th pass qualification
and you will be able to apply in this without any fees,
so keep watching this video,
I am going to give you complete information about it,
so friends let's start
friends, what you are
seeing in the video right now is the official portal of Uttar Pradesh Rojgar
Sangam i.e. the employment office of Uttar Pradesh
and here
you are given information about it which is a
certificate vacancy
i.e. a real vacancy, so the
name of this vacancy has been cemented right here
on their portal, you can see here that the
name of your company is Aditya Birla
Sun Life Insurance Company Limited and if you
talk about posting it here, which is your designation on 30th January 2021, then your  This post has been
advertised for both advisor and offline posts. The
total number of posts is 345 and the last date
for applying is February 5, 2021, which means
you have
very little time to apply.
Therefore, whenever you apply after watching this video,
I will tell you
how you will have to apply. Before that, you should
know the information about the eligibility criteria here. Friends, to
apply for this, only 12th pass
qualification is required from you. If you have passed 12th, then
you can like it. The description of the work is
here, friends, for this you will have
work related to insurance.
You will get the detailed information after being selected.
You
should have Hindi and English knowledge here. If you know
Hindi well or English well,
you can apply for this. The
required category is given here, basically
all career candidates can
apply for this.
What salary will you be given in Ujjain? So
friends, here you will get salary below 10 thousand and
who  Your normal salary will be Rs.8000,
apart from this, you will also be
given a commission according to the policy you have with the insurance company. The minimum age for general
candidates is 18 years and the
maximum age for general candidates is 5 years.
Apart from this, according to government rules,
SC-ST candidates will be given age relaxation of five years
and OBC will be given age relaxation of three years.
Now friends, I would like to tell you
about Unacademy, which is India's
largest learning platform, where you
can take advantage of its Plus idea by joining your Redmi, in which you will be
given live classes through India's top and
best educators sitting at home, you will
get unlimited access to all courses and the
other features that you can see here,
basically you will get the benefit of all these features
with Unacademy Plus, so
what are you waiting for, go quickly and join it,
while signing in, you will get to
use it for dance time, you will get a free
plan unlocked with this.  If you listen to the plus then
you will get a 10% discount in the plan, the
feeling of which is
given to you in the description of the video and let me
tell you that Redmi has brought to you
Unacademy Jaguar Air Force Base
Support 2021, its which is going to
start from February 4, 2021 and will continue till 30, 2030, in this
you will be
admitted through the instructor,
you can see here who will do the permission for which subject, this
educator has a lot of experience
which will help you a lot
in clearing your upcoming exam, along with this
friends, Redmi has brought for you the
complete batch of Mission End 2021 which is
GATE and Mathematics, here friends you will be
admitted by these educators, its
batch will start from February 1, 2020 and will
continue till April 15, 2030, friends
what do you have to do to join, you have to
take the plus session of Air Force Ex and Wide Web and after
its successful completion  At that time,
I told you that I want to use a diesel tank. By
using it,
you will immediately get a ten percent discount. So, what are you waiting for,
friends,
go quickly and you will be added. The link is
given to you in the description of the video. The
medium of education, that is, the medium of your 12th,
should be Hindi here. But let me
tell you that even if you have passed 12th from English medium,
you will still be able to apply.
Friends,
no express information is asked from you to apply, that is, the
candidate can apply in this.
After your selection in the workplace, where will you be posted? So, here
you are told that and keep your hand. Here
you have this posting list and let me tell you
that candidates can apply in this from all India.
Apart from this, friends,
here
you have been given information about your language and you should have
your 12th certificate, that is,
mark sheet.
Your selection will be done
only through interview.
You will not have to take any exam in this.
Here you confirm that on 5 February, if you like this then
you will be able to apply for it. The
place is given here. Basically,
you are being recruited through the employment fair.
Yes, your time is 9:30 in the morning.
Your complete address for this place is
given here. Other details are in
front of you here and the details of the employment fair are also
given to you here. Now let's talk about
how you have to apply for it. Let
me tell you that to apply for it,
first you have to register on this portal. So
here I will
tell you which video you have to watch to get
arrested. I had
made a video on this, you can watch this video here.
In this, you are told step by step the
complete process of how you have to
do this test and how you have to
fill in your qualification information.
I am going to give you the link of this video
in the description of this video. You have to
watch this video and register on this website.
Then you have to open this link
which will be given in the description of the video
and after opening it,
you have to simply click here.  But
you have to like it by clicking on apply, then
your application will be done, you do not need anything else for
this
nor will you
need to give any feedback, if you
face any problem
in filling this form, then you
can ask me by commenting, friends, if you have got
information about which recruitment, I hope you liked this information,
if you have, then please
like and share this video and also subscribe to your own
YouTube channel Gyan The Most and turn on the
bell icon
so that you can get the notification of upcoming videos
first, Jai Hind
friends